[{
  "subject": "Math",
  "classId": "2",
  "roi": [
    {
      "name": "roll",
      "method": "classify",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "-1",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "150",
      "right": "168",
      "top": "28",
      "bottom": "47"
    },
    {
      "name": "roll",
      "method": "classify",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "-1",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "170",
      "right": "188",
      "top": "28",
      "bottom": "46"
    },
    {
      "name": "roll",
      "method": "classify",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "-1",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "190",
      "right": "208",
      "top": "28",
      "bottom": "46"
    },
    {
      "name": "roll",
      "method": "classify",
      "index": "3",
      "row": "-1",
      "col": "-1",
      "left": "211",
      "right": "228",
      "top": "34",
      "bottom": "50"
    },
    {
      "name": "roll",
      "method": "classify",
      "index": "4",
      "row": "-1",
      "col": "-1",
      "left": "231",
      "right": "248",
      "top": "34",
      "bottom": "50"
    },
    {
      "name": "roll",
      "method": "classify",
      "index": "5",
      "row": "-1",
      "col": "-1",
      "left": "251",
      "right": "269",
      "top": "34",
      "bottom": "50"
    },
    {
      "name": "roll",
      "method": "classify",
      "index": "6",
      "row": "-1",
      "col": "-1",
      "left": "271",
      "right": "289",
      "top": "34",
      "bottom": "50"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "1",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "0",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "149",
      "right": "166",
      "top": "98",
      "bottom": "115"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "1",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "0",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "178",
      "right": "196",
      "top": "98",
      "bottom": "115"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "2",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "0",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "149",
      "right": "167",
      "top": "126",
      "bottom": "142"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "2",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "1",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "180",
      "right": "196",
      "top": "126",
      "bottom": "143"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "3",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "2",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "150",
      "right": "167",
      "top": "153",
      "bottom": "168"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "3",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "2",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "180",
      "right": "197",
      "top": "153",
      "bottom": "168"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "4",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "3",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "150",
      "right": "167",
      "top": "179",
      "bottom": "195"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "4",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "3",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "180",
      "right": "197",
      "top": "179",
      "bottom": "195"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "5",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "4",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "150",
      "right": "167",
      "top": "205",
      "bottom": "221"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "5",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "4",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "180",
      "right": "197",
      "top": "206",
      "bottom": "222"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "6",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "5",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "151",
      "right": "168",
      "top": "233",
      "bottom": "249"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "6",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "5",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "180",
      "right": "198",
      "top": "233",
      "bottom": "249"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "7",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "6",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "151",
      "right": "168",
      "top": "259",
      "bottom": "276"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "7",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "6",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "180",
      "right": "198",
      "top": "259",
      "bottom": "276"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "8",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "7",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "151",
      "right": "168",
      "top": "286",
      "bottom": "303"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "8",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "7",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "180",
      "right": "198",
      "top": "287",
      "bottom": "303"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "9",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "8",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "151",
      "right": "168",
      "top": "315",
      "bottom": "332"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "9",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "8",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "181",
      "right": "198",
      "top": "315",
      "bottom": "331"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "10",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "9",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "150",
      "right": "168",
      "top": "342",
      "bottom": "359"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "10",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "9",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "180",
      "right": "198",
      "top": "342",
      "bottom": "359"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "11",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "10",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "150",
      "right": "168",
      "top": "369",
      "bottom": "385"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "11",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "10",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "180",
      "right": "198",
      "top": "369",
      "bottom": "385"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "12",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "11",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "150",
      "right": "167",
      "top": "396",
      "bottom": "412"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "12",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "11",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "180",
      "right": "198",
      "top": "395",
      "bottom": "412"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "13",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "0",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "346",
      "right": "363",
      "top": "99",
      "bottom": "116"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "13",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "0",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "375",
      "right": "392",
      "top": "99",
      "bottom": "116"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "14",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "1",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "345",
      "right": "363",
      "top": "126",
      "bottom": "142"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "14",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "1",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "375",
      "right": "392",
      "top": "126",
      "bottom": "142"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "15",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "2",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "345",
      "right": "363",
      "top": "153",
      "bottom": "169"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "15",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "2",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "375",
      "right": "392",
      "top": "153",
      "bottom": "169"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "16",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "3",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "346",
      "right": "363",
      "top": "179",
      "bottom": "195"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "16",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "3",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "375",
      "right": "392",
      "top": "179",
      "bottom": "195"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "17",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "4",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "346",
      "right": "363",
      "top": "206",
      "bottom": "222"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "17",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "4",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "375",
      "right": "392",
      "top": "206",
      "bottom": "223"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "18",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "5",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "346",
      "right": "362",
      "top": "233",
      "bottom": "250"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "18",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "5",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "375",
      "right": "393",
      "top": "233",
      "bottom": "250"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "19",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "6",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "346",
      "right": "364",
      "top": "260",
      "bottom": "276"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "19",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "6",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "376",
      "right": "392",
      "top": "260",
      "bottom": "276"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "20",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "7",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "348",
      "right": "364",
      "top": "287",
      "bottom": "304"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "20",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "7",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "378",
      "right": "393",
      "top": "287",
      "bottom": "304"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "21",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "8",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "348",
      "right": "364",
      "top": "315",
      "bottom": "331"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "21",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "8",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "378",
      "right": "390",
      "top": "315",
      "bottom": "331"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "22",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "9",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "347",
      "right": "363",
      "top": "342",
      "bottom": "358"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "22",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "9",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "378",
      "right": "394",
      "top": "342",
      "bottom": "358"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "23",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "10",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "347",
      "right": "365",
      "top": "369",
      "bottom": "385"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "23",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "10",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "376",
      "right": "394",
      "top": "369",
      "bottom": "385"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "24",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "11",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "348",
      "right": "365",
      "top": "395",
      "bottom": "411"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "24",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "11",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "377",
      "right": "394",
      "top": "395",
      "bottom": "411"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "25",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "0",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "543",
      "right": "561",
      "top": "98",
      "bottom": "115"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "25",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "0",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "574",
      "right": "591",
      "top": "98",
      "bottom": "115"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "26",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "1",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "544",
      "right": "561",
      "top": "126",
      "bottom": "141"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "26",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "1",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "574",
      "right": "591",
      "top": "125",
      "bottom": "142"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "27",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "2",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "543",
      "right": "561",
      "top": "152",
      "bottom": "168"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "27",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "2",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "573",
      "right": "590",
      "top": "152",
      "bottom": "168"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "28",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "3",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "542",
      "right": "560",
      "top": "179",
      "bottom": "195"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "28",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "3",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "573",
      "right": "590",
      "top": "179",
      "bottom": "195"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "29",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "4",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "543",
      "right": "560",
      "top": "206",
      "bottom": "222"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "29",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "4",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "573",
      "right": "590",
      "top": "206",
      "bottom": "222"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "30",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "5",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "542",
      "right": "560",
      "top": "233",
      "bottom": "249"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "30",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "5",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "573",
      "right": "590",
      "top": "233",
      "bottom": "250"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "31",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "6",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "543",
      "right": "561",
      "top": "260",
      "bottom": "276"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "31",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "6",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "573",
      "right": "591",
      "top": "260",
      "bottom": "277"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "32",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "7",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "543",
      "right": "561",
      "top": "287",
      "bottom": "304"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "32",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "7",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "573",
      "right": "591",
      "top": "287",
      "bottom": "304"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "33",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "8",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "543",
      "right": "562",
      "top": "315",
      "bottom": "332"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "33",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "8",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "573",
      "right": "592",
      "top": "315",
      "bottom": "332"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "34",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "9",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "543",
      "right": "562",
      "top": "342",
      "bottom": "359"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "34",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "9",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "574",
      "right": "592",
      "top": "342",
      "bottom": "359"
    },
    {
      "name": "totalMarks",
      "method": "classify",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "-2",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "342",
      "right": "360",
      "top": "436",
      "bottom": "454"
    },
    {
      "name": "totalMarks",
      "method": "classify",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "-2",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "363",
      "right": "380",
      "top": "436",
      "bottom": "453"
    },
    {
      "name": "totalMarks",
      "method": "classify",
      "index": "2",
      "row": "-2",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "382",
      "right": "400",
      "top": "436",
      "bottom": "453"
    }
  ],
  "extractionMethod": "NUMERIC_CLASSIFICATION",
  "state": "gujrat",
  "roiId": "1"
},{
  "subject": "Hindi",
  "classId": "2",
  "roi": [
    {
      "name": "roll",
      "method": "classify",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "-1",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "150",
      "right": "168",
      "top": "28",
      "bottom": "47"
    },
    {
      "name": "roll",
      "method": "classify",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "-1",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "170",
      "right": "188",
      "top": "28",
      "bottom": "46"
    },
    {
      "name": "roll",
      "method": "classify",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "-1",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "190",
      "right": "208",
      "top": "28",
      "bottom": "46"
    },
    {
      "name": "roll",
      "method": "classify",
      "index": "3",
      "row": "-1",
      "col": "-1",
      "left": "211",
      "right": "228",
      "top": "34",
      "bottom": "50"
    },
    {
      "name": "roll",
      "method": "classify",
      "index": "4",
      "row": "-1",
      "col": "-1",
      "left": "231",
      "right": "248",
      "top": "34",
      "bottom": "50"
    },
    {
      "name": "roll",
      "method": "classify",
      "index": "5",
      "row": "-1",
      "col": "-1",
      "left": "251",
      "right": "269",
      "top": "34",
      "bottom": "50"
    },
    {
      "name": "roll",
      "method": "classify",
      "index": "6",
      "row": "-1",
      "col": "-1",
      "left": "271",
      "right": "289",
      "top": "34",
      "bottom": "50"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "1",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "0",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "149",
      "right": "166",
      "top": "98",
      "bottom": "115"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "1",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "0",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "178",
      "right": "196",
      "top": "98",
      "bottom": "115"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "2",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "0",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "149",
      "right": "167",
      "top": "126",
      "bottom": "142"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "2",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "1",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "180",
      "right": "196",
      "top": "126",
      "bottom": "143"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "3",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "2",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "150",
      "right": "167",
      "top": "153",
      "bottom": "168"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "3",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "2",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "180",
      "right": "197",
      "top": "153",
      "bottom": "168"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "4",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "3",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "150",
      "right": "167",
      "top": "179",
      "bottom": "195"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "4",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "3",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "180",
      "right": "197",
      "top": "179",
      "bottom": "195"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "5",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "4",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "150",
      "right": "167",
      "top": "205",
      "bottom": "221"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "5",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "4",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "180",
      "right": "197",
      "top": "206",
      "bottom": "222"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "6",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "5",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "151",
      "right": "168",
      "top": "233",
      "bottom": "249"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "6",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "5",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "180",
      "right": "198",
      "top": "233",
      "bottom": "249"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "7",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "6",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "151",
      "right": "168",
      "top": "259",
      "bottom": "276"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "7",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "6",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "180",
      "right": "198",
      "top": "259",
      "bottom": "276"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "8",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "7",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "151",
      "right": "168",
      "top": "286",
      "bottom": "303"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "8",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "7",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "180",
      "right": "198",
      "top": "287",
      "bottom": "303"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "9",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "8",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "151",
      "right": "168",
      "top": "315",
      "bottom": "332"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "9",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "8",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "181",
      "right": "198",
      "top": "315",
      "bottom": "331"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "10",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "9",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "150",
      "right": "168",
      "top": "342",
      "bottom": "359"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "10",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "9",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "180",
      "right": "198",
      "top": "342",
      "bottom": "359"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "11",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "10",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "150",
      "right": "168",
      "top": "369",
      "bottom": "385"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "11",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "10",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "180",
      "right": "198",
      "top": "369",
      "bottom": "385"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "12",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "11",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "150",
      "right": "167",
      "top": "396",
      "bottom": "412"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "12",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "11",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "180",
      "right": "198",
      "top": "395",
      "bottom": "412"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "13",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "0",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "346",
      "right": "363",
      "top": "99",
      "bottom": "116"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "13",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "0",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "375",
      "right": "392",
      "top": "99",
      "bottom": "116"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "14",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "1",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "345",
      "right": "363",
      "top": "126",
      "bottom": "142"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "14",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "1",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "375",
      "right": "392",
      "top": "126",
      "bottom": "142"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "15",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "2",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "345",
      "right": "363",
      "top": "153",
      "bottom": "169"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "15",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "2",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "375",
      "right": "392",
      "top": "153",
      "bottom": "169"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "16",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "3",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "346",
      "right": "363",
      "top": "179",
      "bottom": "195"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "16",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "3",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "375",
      "right": "392",
      "top": "179",
      "bottom": "195"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "17",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "4",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "346",
      "right": "363",
      "top": "206",
      "bottom": "222"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "17",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "4",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "375",
      "right": "392",
      "top": "206",
      "bottom": "223"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "18",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "5",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "346",
      "right": "362",
      "top": "233",
      "bottom": "250"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "18",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "5",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "375",
      "right": "393",
      "top": "233",
      "bottom": "250"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "19",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "6",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "346",
      "right": "364",
      "top": "260",
      "bottom": "276"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "19",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "6",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "376",
      "right": "392",
      "top": "260",
      "bottom": "276"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "20",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "7",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "348",
      "right": "364",
      "top": "287",
      "bottom": "304"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "20",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "7",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "378",
      "right": "393",
      "top": "287",
      "bottom": "304"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "21",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "8",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "348",
      "right": "364",
      "top": "315",
      "bottom": "331"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "21",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "8",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "378",
      "right": "390",
      "top": "315",
      "bottom": "331"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "22",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "9",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "347",
      "right": "363",
      "top": "342",
      "bottom": "358"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "22",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "9",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "378",
      "right": "394",
      "top": "342",
      "bottom": "358"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "23",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "10",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "347",
      "right": "365",
      "top": "369",
      "bottom": "385"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "23",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "10",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "376",
      "right": "394",
      "top": "369",
      "bottom": "385"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "24",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "11",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "348",
      "right": "365",
      "top": "395",
      "bottom": "411"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "24",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "11",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "377",
      "right": "394",
      "top": "395",
      "bottom": "411"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "25",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "0",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "543",
      "right": "561",
      "top": "98",
      "bottom": "115"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "25",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "0",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "574",
      "right": "591",
      "top": "98",
      "bottom": "115"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "26",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "1",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "544",
      "right": "561",
      "top": "126",
      "bottom": "141"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "26",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "1",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "574",
      "right": "591",
      "top": "125",
      "bottom": "142"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "27",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "2",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "543",
      "right": "561",
      "top": "152",
      "bottom": "168"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "27",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "2",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "573",
      "right": "590",
      "top": "152",
      "bottom": "168"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "28",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "3",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "542",
      "right": "560",
      "top": "179",
      "bottom": "195"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "28",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "3",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "573",
      "right": "590",
      "top": "179",
      "bottom": "195"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "29",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "4",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "543",
      "right": "560",
      "top": "206",
      "bottom": "222"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "29",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "4",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "573",
      "right": "590",
      "top": "206",
      "bottom": "222"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "30",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "5",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "542",
      "right": "560",
      "top": "233",
      "bottom": "249"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "30",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "5",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "573",
      "right": "590",
      "top": "233",
      "bottom": "250"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "31",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "6",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "543",
      "right": "561",
      "top": "260",
      "bottom": "276"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "31",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "6",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "573",
      "right": "591",
      "top": "260",
      "bottom": "277"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "32",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "7",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "543",
      "right": "561",
      "top": "287",
      "bottom": "304"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "32",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "7",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "573",
      "right": "591",
      "top": "287",
      "bottom": "304"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "33",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "8",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "543",
      "right": "562",
      "top": "315",
      "bottom": "332"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "33",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "8",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "573",
      "right": "592",
      "top": "315",
      "bottom": "332"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "34",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "9",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "543",
      "right": "562",
      "top": "342",
      "bottom": "359"
    },
    {
      "name": "marks",
      "method": "classify",
      "question": "34",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "9",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "574",
      "right": "592",
      "top": "342",
      "bottom": "359"
    },
    {
      "name": "totalMarks",
      "method": "classify",
      "index": "0",
      "row": "-2",
      "col": "0",
      "left": "342",
      "right": "360",
      "top": "436",
      "bottom": "454"
    },
    {
      "name": "totalMarks",
      "method": "classify",
      "index": "1",
      "row": "-2",
      "col": "1",
      "left": "363",
      "right": "380",
      "top": "436",
      "bottom": "453"
    },
    {
      "name": "totalMarks",
      "method": "classify",
      "index": "2",
      "row": "-2",
      "col": "2",
      "left": "382",
      "right": "400",
      "top": "436",
      "bottom": "453"
    }
  ],
  "extractionMethod": "NUMERIC_CLASSIFICATION",
  "state": "gujrat",
  "roiId": "2"
}]